<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science Portfolio on Sarbojit Das</title>
    <link>https:///www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science Portfolio on Sarbojit Das</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 11:00:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https:///www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 6: Covid-19 X-Ray predictor</title>
      <link>https:///www.example.com/post/project-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:///www.example.com/post/project-6/</guid>
      <description>•	Implement a tool that classifies whether a lung is affected by pneumonia due to covid-19
•	Images are collected from different resources such as hospital, medical center etc and jupyter and python are used to load the images
•	Features of images are preprocessed, standardized and normalized.
•	Tensor flow is used to build CNN model to predict the output
•	This model is used in app and web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 5: Sound Classifier</title>
      <link>https:///www.example.com/post/project-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:///www.example.com/post/project-5/</guid>
      <description>•	Build a tool that can classify different environmental sound based different features.
•	A dataset is fetched from the data storage kaggle and load the dataset using python.
•	Different machine learning algorithm are used to train the model and compare the performance of the model and select the best fit model.
•	Finally, import the model into different apps.
 The github url for this project: https://github.com/sarbojitdas/sound_classifier</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 4: Loan Qualifier System</title>
      <link>https:///www.example.com/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:///www.example.com/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>•Implement a tool that classifies the loan status whether it is in collection or paid-off.
•A survey is conducted on different students and a dataset is prepared and loaded to the system using python.
•Logistic Regression, Support Vector Machine and Decision Tree are used to train the model and choose the best fit model.
•Finally the model is imported into an app or a web.
 The github url for this project: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 3: Dress recommendation System</title>
      <link>https:///www.example.com/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2016 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:///www.example.com/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>•Create a tool that can recommend a dress or not based on certain features.
•A general survey is conducted to prepare the dataset and python is used to read and load the dataset.
•Logistic Regression, Naïve Bayes and Support vector machine are used to prepare model and comparethe performance and select the best fit model.
•Finally import the model into apps or webs.
 The github url for this project: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Wheat Classifier</title>
      <link>https:///www.example.com/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:///www.example.com/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>•Implement a tool that can classify different species of wheat based on certain attributes.
•A dataset is prepared based on survey and dataset is loaded and read using python on Jupiter platform.
•K Nearest Neighbor, Decision Tree and Support Vector Machine are used to train the model and select the best fir model.
•Finally, import the model into apps or webs.
 The github url for this project: https://github.com/sarbojitdas/Wheat_classifier</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Company Customer churns predictor</title>
      <link>https:///www.example.com/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:///www.example.com/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>• Create a tool that predicts whether a company retains its customer or churns its customer so that company can change its business policy.
• Customer details are fetched and loaded to the system using python and jupyter.
• Features from the text of each customer description classify the customer orientation.
• Random Forest, Naïve Bayes and Support Vector are used and compare the performance of each model and finally select the best fit model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https:///www.example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:///www.example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media platforms.
   Platform URL     YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/c/sarbojitdas?sub_confirmation=1   Twitter: https://twitter.com/sarbojitdas_ece   LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarbojit-das-a3b2994b/   GitHub: https://github.com/sarbojitdas   Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sarbojit.das.3/   Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/sarbojit19/    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
